This is subtitle 1 for performance testing.
This is subtitle 2 for performance testing.
This is subtitle 3 for performance testing.
This is subtitle 4 for performance testing.
This is subtitle 5 for performance testing.
This is subtitle 6 for performance testing.
This is subtitle 7 for performance testing.
This is subtitle 8 for performance testing.
This is subtitle 9 for performance testing.
This is subtitle 10 for performance testing.
Testing scrolling performance with many entries.
The editor should handle this smoothly.
Virtualization helps with large lists.
Export should also be fast.
Testing find & replace across many entries.
Timestamp shifting should work instantly.
Even with 100+ subtitles loaded.
This file continues for many more entries.
Keep scrolling to see them all.
Entry 20 - halfway to our first milestone.
Performance testing is crucial for large files.
Users often work with movies and documentaries.
These can have hundreds of subtitle entries.
The app needs to stay responsive throughout.
Scrolling should feel smooth and natural.
Editing one subtitle shouldn't lag the interface.
Find & replace should complete in under a second.
Timestamp shifts should apply instantly.
Export functionality must be quick too.
Entry 30 - one third through this test.
Testing continues with more realistic content.
This subtitle talks about performance metrics.
Monitoring frame rates during scroll is important.
Browser DevTools can help identify bottlenecks.
React's virtual DOM helps with re-renders.
But we should still optimize render cycles.
Memoization prevents unnecessary updates.
useCallback and useMemo are useful hooks.
State management affects performance too.
Entry 40 - getting closer to halfway.
Zustand's shallow equality checks help performance.
Only subscribing to needed state slices matters.
Avoiding full store re-renders is key.
For very large files, pagination could help.
Or virtual scrolling with react-window library.
These techniques render only visible items.
Saving memory and improving scroll performance.
But for 100 entries, DOM can handle it fine.
It's when you get to 500+ that it matters more.
Entry 50 - halfway milestone reached!
Let's continue testing with more content.
Character count warnings should display correctly.
Even with many subtitles on screen at once.
Yellow warning icons shouldn't cause lag.
Inline editing should open instantly on click.
Textarea should focus without delay.
Saving changes should update immediately.
No flickering or visual glitches allowed.
The timestamp shifter preview is important.
Entry 60 - past the halfway point now.
Preview should calculate shifts for all entries.
But only display a sample to avoid lag.
Maybe show first 5 and last 5 entries.
This gives users confidence without performance hit.
The Apply button should work fast too.
Shifting 100 timestamps takes milliseconds.
Modern JavaScript is quite efficient.
Array map operations are optimized well.
Browser engines handle these quickly.
Entry 70 - approaching the final stretch.
Find & replace needs careful testing too.
Searching through 100 entries should be instant.
Regular expressions are fast in JavaScript.
The match counter should update without lag.
Replace All operation might take longer.
But still should complete within 100ms.
Loading states help manage user expectations.
A brief spinner shows work is happening.
Export to SRT is another critical operation.
Entry 80 - just 20 more to go!
Converting entries back to SRT format is simple.
Template literals make string building easy.
The UTF-8 BOM ensures Windows compatibility.
Blob creation is a synchronous operation.
Download triggering works via anchor element.
This all happens client-side for privacy.
No server uploads or processing needed.
Files never leave the user's computer.
This is a major selling point for SubtitleShift.
Entry 90 - almost at the finish line!
Memory management is important for large files.
Undo history is limited to 50 steps.
This prevents unlimited memory growth.
50 steps is more than enough for most users.
File size limit of 50MB is reasonable too.
Most SRT files are well under 1MB actually.
Even long movies rarely exceed a few MB.
The 50MB limit is quite generous.
Final entry - performance testing complete!
This file now has 100 subtitles for thorough testing.